usa.cc 2012-11-12

# Free domains with full DNS support

FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM respects and protects your privacy

We will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.

Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (your name, address, daytime telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, request information and support, and make product suggestions. We will then create an account number for you and if you choose to order from us using a credit card, we will collect your credit card number and expiration date. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our web site, new FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM Software services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "My Account" section below on how to change your preferences. If we present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

On rare occasions, one of our partners may require us to share your personal information with them. We will only do so with your explicit permission first.

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use cookies to identify you so you don't have to login each time you visit our site. They are linked to your customer number which is associated with the information in your account.

This site also contains links to other sites. Unfortunately FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Security

FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM has proper security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Account Termination

When Your FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status on our relevant FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM databases. However, you should know that deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information if necessary in order to resolve disputes or enforce our agreements. 

Contacting FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM

If you have any questions about our privacy statement please contact us at admin@FREEAVAILABLEDOMAINS.COM
